Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Maquiladora/Sweatshop Campaigns, 1983-2008; Series 4
  - Maquila and Trade Research Materials, 1988-2012; Series 4 Subseries 4
    - New Hampshire (9), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey (10), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - New Mexico (11), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 22)
    - New York (12), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Ohio (13), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 24)
    - Oklahoma (14), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 25)
    - Oregan (15), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 26)
    - Rhode Island/AFL-CIO (16), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 27)
    - Tennessee (17), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 171, Folder 28)
    - Texas (18), 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Utah (19), 1992-1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Levi's, Koramsa, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - ORIT Women's Division, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Oxford Industries, Inc., 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Rampage Clothing Company, 1992-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - RNs-Santana Ltd., 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Sportex, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Social Investors-KLD (Kinder, Lydenberg, Domini), 1992-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Textile and Apparel reports, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Wal-Mart, 1992-1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - women for Guatemala, Weavers' Project, 1992-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Women Trade Unionist delegation materials, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers union--Donna Mandel report, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Association for Women in Development (AWID) conference, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Bodek and Rhodes, 1993-2000; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Campaign for a Global Minimum Wage, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Committee for International Human Rights Inquiry, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - CODEHUCA, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Esdee, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - Foxcraft Industries, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - "Free Trade's Hidden Secrets"-NLC report, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - Guatemala-Agroport, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - Guatemala maquila brochure drafts, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala Maquila Worker Education seminar, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala Maquila Worker's Tour-Olimpia Gatica, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala-Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1993-2002; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Grieder Sales and Brokerage, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Hampton Industries, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - H.B. Fuller Company, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - The Human Face of Work-Mexico Maquilas, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Industries RCA, 1993-2001; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Investors Firms-Calvaert Asset Management Company, Inc., 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Investors Firms-Franklin Research and Development Corporation, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Investors Responsibility Research Center. Inc., 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - JC Penny, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Labor Notes, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Land's End, Inc., 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Leslie Fay, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - LL Bean, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Maquila Solidarity Network, Women to Women, 1993-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - NAFTA and Caribbean Basin countries, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Topsville, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Trade/Maquila bibliographic sources, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - United Garment Workers, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - Welly's, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - Women Trade Unionist delegation, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - Working Assets Capital Management, 1993-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Association of Women in the Textile Industry of Guatemala (AMITEG), 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Central America campaign packet, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - CERIGUA maquila study, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Child Labor Coalition, 1994-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Christian Task Force on Central America, 1994-2003; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Cimatex, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Responsibility-Presbyterian Church, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Cortex, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Del Prado, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Edison Brothers Stores, Inc., 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - GHR Industries, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - GHR Industries/Marissa, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala-Cygene Designs, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Guatemala-Cygene Designs/JMB International, 1994-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Guatemala-Empresa Exacta, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Guatemala-Goodyear, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Guatemala-maquila documentary correspondence, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Guatemala-maquila information, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Guatemala-SAMDO exporter, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala-STITCH, Jennifer Hill, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala-Warner-Lambert Company, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 21)
    - ITGWLF Codes of Conduct Summary, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - Interviews by Henry J. Frundt, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - JC Penny/CMT, 1994-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - Label Letter, AFL-CIO, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - Labor and Worker Rights Bulletin on Guatemala, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - Levi's Action Kit, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 26)
    - Levi's Research Report, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 27)
    - Levi Strauss and Company conduct, 1994-2005; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 28)
    - Maquila address list, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 29)
    - Maquila Support-Garret Brown, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - Maquila worker interviews, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Maquila worker surveys, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Magneto, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Mexico-General Electric/Compania Armadora (CASA), 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Mexico-Sony [1/2], 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Mexico-Sony [2/2], 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Nicaraguan Maquilas, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Reebok reports, 1994-1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - UNSITRAGUA advertisement, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Women to Women Correspondencia, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Women's Organizing in Guatemala, 1994-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - 21 of June Labor Conference, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Apparel Trade Statistics, 1995-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - El Salvador labor interviews-Henry J. Frundt, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Gap, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - G.H.R. Industries/JC Penny, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - G.H.R. Industries/Kmart, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - G.H.R. Industries/Portnoy, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - G.H.R. Industries-Negotiations, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - G.H.R. Industries/Sears, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - G.H.R. Industries/Target, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - G.H.R. Industries/Walmart, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - Guatemala-CAPRITEX, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala Monitoring, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala maquila response to GSP, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala maquila violence, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Guatemala non-PVH Press, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Guatemala -Shin Kwang Clothing, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Honduras Memorandum of Understanding, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Honduras-Yuttwa, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - ICCR-David Schilling/Coca-Cola, 1995-2002; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - INAPSA, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - INAPSA Allies, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Independent Monitoring proposals, 1995-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Industrias RCA-Gomez, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility-Principles for Global corporate Responsibility, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Investor Firms-Massachusetts Financial Services Company, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Investor Responsibility Research Center-Worker Standards, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Jornadas Sindicales 21 de Junio, Guatemala, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Korean Textile Investments, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Korea/Guatemala Workers, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - London trip, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Maquila research, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Maquila Solidarity Network, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Marissa-Action, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Marissa-Grassroots, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Marissa-Materials, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 25)
    - Marissa-Materials, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 26)
    - Miscellanous Maquila, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 176, Folder 27)
    - MJ Modas, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Multinational Monitor drafts, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - National Retail Federation, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Nicaragua-Kathie Lee, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - President Clinton-sweatshop codes of conduct, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - South/north Conference: New Alliances for Dignity in Labor, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - STITCH/Erich Han, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Sysco Corporation/Sara Lee Corporation reports, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Toy Campaign, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - USTR November delegation, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Verite Information packet, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Worker Education Proposal, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Business for Social Responsibility, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Canadian Catholic Organization for Development and Peace, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Chicago area media, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Jobs with Justice, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladoras, 1996-2003; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Debora Guzman-threats, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Eddie Baur, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - GLEP-Martin, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Gonzalez-Housing Leads, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Guatemala-Aurea/Amsport, Inc., 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala-GHR Industries, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala-Juana Modas, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Honduras-Kimi, 1996-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Honduras-Maquila research, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Inexport, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Investor Responsibility Research Center-research, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Independent Monitoring Working Group, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Liz Clairbone, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Maquila research, 1996-2002; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Merry-Go-Round Enterprises, Inc., 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous maquila, 1996-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Nicaragua-maquilas, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Nicaragua-Nicseda, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Pedro Ortega and Rodolfo Robles, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez [1], 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez [2], 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez [3], 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-Canada, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-DC Trip, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-Guatemala Trip, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-Meeting Notes, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 22)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-Plane Tickets, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 23)
    - Reynaldo Gonzalez-Visa, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - Sweatshop summit, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Stop Sweatshop News, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - "Trade and Cross-Border Labor Strategies in the Americas" by Henry J. Frundt, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Vilma Gonzalez, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Vilma Cristina Gonzalez, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Vilma & Reynaldo Gonzalez-Alerts, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Wal-Mart/Kathie Lee Gifford, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO-Stan Gacek, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - California-Guess?, Inc., 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Cambodia, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Cambodia-Sam Han Facotry/Montgomery Ward and Co., 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Carole Little-California Fashion Industries, Incorporated, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Child Labor-Foul Ball Campaign, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Child Labor-RUGMARK, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Christian Aid-NGO Campaigning on Trade Issues, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - Council on Economic Priorities Accreditation Agency (CEPAA), 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - COVERCO, 1997-2003; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - Daimi [1/2], 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - Daimi [2/2], 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - Esprit, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - Federated Department Stores-Kimi, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - Garment Industry Trendsetters, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Global Economics and Human Rights in Action conference, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Global Sweatshop Curriculum packet-Campaign for Labor Rights, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Gonzalez report, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Han Young maquila, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - ICFTU Codes of Conduct, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Kimi/Rosenthal=Congoleum, 1997-1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Labor and Social Justice conference, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Letter of Inquiry-Notes, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Linda Yanz, Women's Network, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Maquilas, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Maquila codes of conduct, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Maquila Network Update, 1997-2004; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Maquila Workers, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Mi Kwang Plastics Company, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - National Center of rht Laity conference, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Nike, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Nicaragua, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Religious contacts, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Retail, Wholesale, and Department store Union, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - STITCH, Methodist Church, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Twenty-One International, Incorporated, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Sweatshops-White House Task Force, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Western Illinois University, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - White House Apparel Industry Partnership, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Alliance for the Monitoring and Support of Social Responsibility (AMARS), 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Apparel Imports, 1998-2000; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Apparel Industry Partnership agreement, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Apparel Industry Partnership-codes of conduct, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Apparel Industry Partnership-debate, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Back to Basics conference, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Brussels meeting, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Business for Social Responsibility (BSR), 1998-2002; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Campaign to Defend Labor Rights in Export Processing Plants, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Campaign for Labor Rights-Trim Bissell, 1998-2002; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Cerigua Weekly Briefs-Mujeres en la Solidaridad, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - DSA Conference, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - EU Symposium-Monitoring Codes of Conduct, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - FITTVCC Guatemala (1), 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - FITTVCC Project (2), 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - FITTVCC Consultation (3), 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Global Labor Standards and the Apparel Industry-Harvard Trade Union Program, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Graphics-Ad book, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - ILRF/Coverco, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Living Wage Working Summit, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Maquilas-Tina Sorenson/Tasha, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Mi Kwang Plastics Company, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - National Labor Committee-Wal-Mart Campaign, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Pesquera, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Reflections on Independent Monitoring, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Rifle Industries-Enzo Carlino, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco trip notes, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - STITCH Delegation, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Sweatshop Victory/Child Labor March, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - toys R Us, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - University of Chicago contacts, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - UNITe Anti-Sweatshop retreat, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Apparel Industry Partnership, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Bodek and Rhodes, Carrousel Trading Company, Inc., 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Bodek and Rhodes correspondence, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - The Case of the Bandegua Workers, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Central America labor research, 1999-2001; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Champion, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Clean Clothes Campaign, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Council on Economic Priorities proposal, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Council on Economic Priorities Accreditation Agency SA 8000, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Fair Labor Association, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - FITTVCC/UNITE, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Forum evaluation, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - GEAR, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Germany trip, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Global Exchange-Directory of U.S. Anti-Sweatshop Organizations, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Gua de Observacin de Eventos Sindicales, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Guide to SEC Filings, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Hesperian Foundation Library-maquila, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Invitation-labor conditions discussion, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - The Maquiladora Reader-American Friends Service Committee, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 183, Folder 13)